Guide to the Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive 1961-2009 (bulk 1976-2005) MSS.171
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Artists Files
  - Marisol [1 of 2], undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Marisol [2 of 2], undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Marisol, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Marisol, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Maron, Jeffrey, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Maron, Jeffrey, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Maron, Jeffrey, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Marshall, Kerry James, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Martin, Walter, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Martin, Walter, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Martin, Younghee Choi, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Martinez-Canas, Maria, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Masayesva, Victor, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Matthews, Victor, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Matzko, Claudia - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Matzko, Claudia - Photos/Slides, 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Matzko, Claudia - Review, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Maxwell, William, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Mayercak, Zdeno - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Mayercak, Zdeno - Photos/Slides, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - McBride, Rita, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - McCarthy, Kathleen, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - McCarthy, Kathleen, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - McCaslin, Matthew, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - McClelland, Suzanne, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - McCollum, Allan [1 of 2], undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - McCollum, Allan [2 of 2], undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - McCollum, Allan, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - McCollum, Allan, undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - McCoy, Ann, undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - McCoy, Ann, undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - McElheny, Josiah, undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - McGowin, Ed, undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - McGowin, Ed, undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - McGowin, Ed [1 of 3], undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - McGowin, Ed [2 of 3], undated (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - McGowin, Ed [3 of 3], undated (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - McKie, Judy Kensley, undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - McKie, Judy Kensley, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Medel, Rebecca - Photos/Slides, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Medel, Rebecca - Reviews, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Meehan, Kathleen, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Mehretu, Julie - Reviews, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Meireles, Cildo, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Melchert, Jim, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Mendelson, Shari - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Merz, Mario, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Merz, Mario, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Messager, Annette, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Messner, Ann, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Messner, Ann, 1990-1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Meyer, Franz, 2001, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Meyer, Syd, 1998, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Migdoll, Herbert, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Migdoll, Herbert, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Mikami, Seiko, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Miller, Ross, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Milow, Keith, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Minter, Marilyn, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Miss, Mary [1 of 2], undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Miss, Mary [2 of 2], undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Miss, Mary [1 of 2], undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Miss, Mary [2 of 2], undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Mitchell, Tyrone, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Miyawaki, Aiko [1 of 2], undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Miyawaki, Aiko [2 of 2], undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Miyawaki, Aiko, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Mizu, Odoru, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Moffatt, Tracy - Invitations, Bio/, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Mol, Pieter Laurens, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Monteavaro, Beatriz - Photos/Slides (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Monteavaro, Beatriz - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Monteavaro, Beatriz (CD), undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Moore, Graeme, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Moore, Henry, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Morellet, Francois, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Morgan, Jennifer - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Morgan, Jennifer - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Mori, Mariko - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2003 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Mori, Mariko - Reviews, 1997, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Morley, Malcolm, undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Morley, Malcolm, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Morrel, Owen - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Morrel, Owen, undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Morrel, Owen - Photos/Slides, 1991-1994 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Morrel, Owen - Reviews, 1991-1998 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Morrill, Michael, undated (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Morrill, Michael, 1984-1990 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Morrill, Michael - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Morrill, Michael, undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Morris, Robert - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., undated (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Morris, Robert - Photos/Slides, 1981-1983 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Morris, Robert, undated (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Morris, Robert - Kansas City, undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Morris, Robert - Pittsburgh, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Morris Proposals, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Morris, Robert, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Morris, Robert, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Mosher, Kirsten, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Motherwell, Robert, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Moulton, Donn, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Mouraud, Tania - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Mouraud, Tania - Reviews, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Mullican, Matt - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Mullican, Matt, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Mullican, Matt, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Mullican, Matt, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Mullin, Martin - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Mullin, Martin - Photos/Slides, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Muniz, Vik, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Muniz, Vik - Reviews, 1989-1998 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Muniz, Vik - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Muniz, Vik - Photos/Slides, 1995-2000 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Munoz, Celia Alvarez, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Munoz, Celia Alvarez - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1991 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Munoz, Celia Alvarez - Reviews, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Munoz, Juan - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Munoz, Juan - Photos/Slides, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Muntadas, Antoni - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Murakami, Takashi - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997-2001 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Murakami, Takashi - Reviews, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Murase, Scott & Robert - Photos/Slides, 1999-2002 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Murase, Scott & Robert - Reviews, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Murase, Scott & Robert - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Murch, Anna Valentina - Photos/Slides, 1986-1997 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Murch, Anna Valentina - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1987-1998 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Murch, Anna Valentina - Reviews, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Murray, Elizabeth - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1995-2006 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Murray, Elizabeth - Photos/Slides, 1981-1984 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Murray, Robert, undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Murray, Robert - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Murray, Robert - Photos/Slides, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Murrill, Gwynn, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Murrill, Gwynn - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Murrill, Gwynn - Photos/Slides, 1980-1994 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Murrill, Gwynn - Reviews, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Mutal, Lika, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Myers, Forrest - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Nagasawa, Nobuho - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Nagasawa, Nobuho - Reviews, 1988-1992 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Nagel, Andres, undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Nagel, Andres - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Nagel, Andres - Photos/Slides, 1985-1992 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Nagel, Andres - Reviews, 1993-1995 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Nagel, Andres - Proposals, undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Nagy, Peter - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Nagy, Peter - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Nahon, Brigitte - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Nahon, Brigette - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Nahon, Brigette - Reviews, undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Nahon, Brigette - Proposals, undated (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Nash, David - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996-2005 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Nash, David - Reviews, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Nash, David - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_3a3c4a08d7cbb13849e9e9e9f4d2401f)
  - Nauman, Bruce - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Nauman, Bruce - Photos/S;odes, 1977-1988 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Nauman, Bruce - Reviews, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Negret, Edgar - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Neidich, Warren - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003-2005 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Neijna, Barbara, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Nelson, Judd - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Nelson, Judd - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Nelson, Judd - Reviews, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Neri, Manuel - Reviews, 1971-1984 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Neri, Manuel - Photos/Slides, 1985-1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Neri, Manuel - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1988 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Neri, Manuel [2 of 2], undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Neri, Manuel #1 [1 of 3], undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Neri, Manuel #2 [2 of 3], undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Neri, Manuel #3 [3 of 3], undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Neto, Ernesto - Reviews, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Neto, Ernesto - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2000-2003 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Netto, Vanilla - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2004 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Neuhaus, Max - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1987-2001 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Neuhaus, Max - Reviews, 1979-1987 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Neuhaus, Max, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Nevelson, Louise - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Nevelson, Louise - Articles, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Nevelson, Louise - B/W Photos, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Nevelson, Louise - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Nevelson, Louise, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Nevelson, Louise - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Nevelson, Louise - Reviews, 1988-1998 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Nevelson, Maria - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Nevelson, Maria - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Nevelson, Maria Isak, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Newman, John Avery - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Newman, John - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Newman, John - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Newman, John - Reviews, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Nice, Don, undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Nicholson, Roy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Nicol, Heather - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2001-2004 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Nicol, Heather - Photos/Slides, 1993-1998 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Nicol, Heather - Reviews, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Nicosia, Nic, undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Nigro, Samuel - Photos/Slides, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Nigro, Samuel - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Noguchi, Isamu, undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Noguchi, Isamu - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Noguchi, Isamu - Photos/Slides, 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Noguchi, Isamu, undated (Box 23, Folder 49A)
  - Noire, Marco, undated (Box 23, Folder 49B)
  - Noland, Cady - Reviews, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Noland, Ken - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Noland, Kenneth - Photos/Slides, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Noland, Kenneth - Reviews, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Noland, Ken, undated (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Nonas, Richard - Photos/Slides, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Nonas, Richard - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1989 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Nonas, Richard - Reviews, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Nonas, Richard, undated (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Nordman, Maria - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Nordman, Maria - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Nordman, Maria - Reviews, 1979-1991 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Nordman, Maria - Photos/Slides, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Norvell, Patsy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Norvell, Patsy - Photos/Slides, 1981-1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Norvell, Patsy - Reviews, 1980-1983 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Norvell, Patsy - Proposals, 1983-1992 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Norzick, Lori - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Novros, David - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Novros, David - Reviews, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Novros, David - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Novros, David, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Obrosey, Aric - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Obrosey, Aric - Reviews, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Obrosey, Aric - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - O'Doherty, Brian, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Oehlen, Albert - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Oehlen, Albert - Photos/Slides, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Oldenburg, Claes, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Oldenburg, Claes, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Oldenburg, Claes - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Oldenburg, Claes - Reviews, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Oldenburg, Claes - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Oleszko, Pat - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Oleszko, Pat - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Oppenheim, Dennis - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 1996-1999 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Oppenheim, Dennis (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Oppenheim, Dennis (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Oppenheim, Dennis - Reviews, 1990-2003 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Oppenheim, Dennis - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Opie, Julian, undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Orozco, Gabriel - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 1997-2002 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Orozco, Gabriel - Photos/Slides, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Orozco, Gabriel - Reviews, 1996-2001 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Osorio, Pepon - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Otterson, Joel - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Otterness, Tom - Reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Otterness, Tom, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Otterness, Tom - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 1985-2005 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Otterness, Tom - Photos/Slides cont., undated (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Otterness, Tom - Photos/Slides, 1982-1994 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Oursler, Tony - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., undated (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Oursler, Tony - Reviews, undated (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Oursler, Tony - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Paik, Nam June - Reviews, undated (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Paik, Nam June - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., undated (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Paik, Nam June - Photos/Slides, 1986-1992 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Paik, Nam June, undated (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Paine, Roxy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Paine, Roxy - Photos/Slides, 1993-1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Paine, Roxy - Reviews, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Paine, Roxy, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Paladino, Mimmo - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Paladino, Mimmo - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Paladino, Mimmo - Reviews, 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Paladino, Mimmo, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Paley, Albert, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Pang, Sze Lin - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2002 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Pang, Sze Lin - Photos/Slides, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Paolini, Giulio, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Paolini, Giulio, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Pardo, Jorge, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Pardo, Jorge - Photos/Slides, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Pardo, Jorge - Reviews, 1996-2006 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Pardo, Jorge - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Parker, Erik - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2000 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Pels, Marsha, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Penk, A. R., undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Penone, Giuseppe - "Critical Material" [1 of 2], undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Penone, Giuseppe - "Sheraton Project" [2 of 2], undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Penone, Giuseppe, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Penone, Giuseppe, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Penone, Giuseppe, undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Penone - Viscals, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Pepper, Beverly - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2003 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Pepper, Beverly - Photos/Slides, 1978-1992 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Pepper, Beverly - Reviews, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Perry, Beatrice, undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Pfaff, Judy #1 [1 of 2], undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Pfaff, Judy #2 [2 of 2], undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Pfaff, Judy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 1982-2005 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Pfaff, Judy - Photos/Slides, 1985-1996 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Pfaff, Judy - Reviews, 1980-2005 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Pfaff, Judy, undated (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Phalle, Niki - Photos/Slides, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Phalle, Niki - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2001 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Phillips, David, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Phillips, Liz, undated (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Picasso, Pablo, undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Picasso, Pablo - Reviews, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Piccillio, undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Pierogi - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2000-2005 (Box 25, Folder 43a)
  - Pierre, Vicki - Photos/Slides, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Pierre, Vickie - Reviews, undated (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Pierre, Vickie - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Pierson, Jack - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Pierson, Jack - Reviews, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Piffman, Lari, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Pihlblad, Janet - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Pihlblad, Janet - Photos/Slides, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Pihlblad, Janet - Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Pil Yun, Ahn, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Pinto, Jody [1 of 2], undated (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Pinto, Jody [2 of 2], undated (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Pinto, Jody - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1985-1997 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Pinto, Jody - Photos/Slides, 1980-1999 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Pinto, Jody - Reviews, 1977-2000 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Pinto, Jody - Proposals, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Pipps, Rodney - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1995 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Pistoletto, Michelangelo - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1980-1994 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Pistoletto, Michelangelo - Photos/Slides, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Pistoletto, Michelangelo - Reviews, 1980-1989 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Plensa, Juame - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Plensa, Juame - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Plensa, Juame, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Plensa, Juame - Reviews, 1989-2001 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc. cont., 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc. cont., 1990-1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994-2004 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick [1 of 2], undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick [2 of 2], undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Reviews cont., 1984-1989 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Proposals, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Financial Records, 1986-1995 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Photos/Slides cont., undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Reviews, 1990-1999 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick, undated (Box 26, Folder 18a)
  - Pollack, J.S. - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Pollack, J.S. - Photos/Slides, 1992-1995 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Pollack, J.S. - Reviews, 1988-1994 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Pomeroy, Jordana, undated (Box 26, Folder 21a)
  - Pomodoro, Arnaldo, undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Pomodoro, Arnaldo - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Pondick, Rona - Reviews, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Porter, Katherine, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Pospisil, Jack, undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Potoff, Reeva, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Potrc, Marjetica - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Pousette-Dart, Joanna, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Prentice, Tim - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Price, Ken, undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Pruitt, Early, undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Puett, J. Morgan, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Puryear, Martin - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Puryear, Martin - Reviews, undated (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Puryear, Martin, undated (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Puryear, Martin - Photos/Slides, 1977-1995 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Puryear, Martin, undated (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Quaytman, Rebecca, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Quiang, Cai Guo, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Rahmani, Aviva, 2000-2002 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Rakowitz, Michael - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Rakowitz, Michael - Reviews, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Ramirez, Paul Henry - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Ramirez, Paul Henry - Reviews, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Rankin, Amanda, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Rapson, Sarah - Reviews, 1999-2001 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Rapson, Sarah - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2001 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Rath, Alan - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 11)